He’s a serial killer.
We’ll take him in dead or alive.
Asura gave me the right
to decide the ending.
Which means I, as the creator,
am the only person who knows the password.
I have a video.
I’ll take them down.
I don’t care
which big shot is behind this.
Release? How?
The evidence is obviously against him.
I think something is getting fishy.
You should contact Nop right away.
Inspector.
We’ve found that the victim’s wallet,
gun, and all valuables are gone.
I suspect it is a robbery gone wrong.
I’ll think about
Asura’s password on my own.
You should rest.
It’s okay.
I’m fine.
Phat.
You’re allowed to be weak.
You don’t have to carry everything
on your own.
Oh, Inspector.
Good timing, sir.
Hang on a minute.
You have a parcel.
Here.
Thank you.
NOPPHAN KONGKRAM
Nop.
How was it? Everything okay?
DSI has examined the evidence.
They took the case.
Kitti won’t get away with it this time.
(Praew has been discharged.)
Thank you.
The doctor said Praew can come home now.
I’ll go to the hospital with you.
Let’s go.
He’s waiting for you, sir.
I’m sorry, sir.
I’ve made a mess.
But your nephew was partly to blame.
I know my nephew well.
I’m not evading responsibility
by blaming anyone.
I’m just saying
we all play a part in this.
But I can handle this and get it done
if you can promise me
Inspector Phat won’t get in the way again.
The doctor said
you can go home now, Praew.
Kaye and I are here to take you home.
You want me to go home
and get on with my life
when my friend is still here like this?
Praew.
I understand what you’ve been through.
But it’s over now.
Piaw is dead.
Yeah, he did.
No freaking thanks to the police.
Don’t you think it’s funny that
while that asshole was hurting my friend,
all I could do was lie there?
And the person who saved me
wasn’t even a cop.
An asshole like you…
deserves to die.
That day
I wasn’t afraid of Nekros at all.
Praew.
He’s a murderer.
But that scumbag deserved his end
and you know it.
Do you want to live in a world
where what is wrong or right
is decided by how you feel
and what you believe in?
Vigilante punishment.
No laws.
Just death sentences without judgement.
Do you really want that?
But laws are useless against these scums!
If it wasn’t for Nekros,
you’d have found Prim and me as corpses.
You know what?
Someone who’s never been a victim like you
would never understand.
Yes, Uncle?
(I just got news that Kitti
was on to your scheme and has escaped.)
But what tipped him off?
Let’s not worry about that.
I’ll have him hunted down.
Phat.
You need to be careful from now on.
Talk to me before you take any actions.
Do you understand?
(Yes, Uncle.)
Someone tipped Kitti off about the arrest.
He caught on before he got booked.
Phat.
You know what they did to Nop.
If you keep on pushing like this,
I fear you’d be their next kill.
Do you want Nop to die for nothing?
Listen, Kaye.
I don’t care what big shot
is behind Kitti,
I’m dragging his ass out into the light.
Did the doctor take your mouth?
Come on.
Smile for me.
Kaye said he’d love to buy you
dinner some time.
You’re living the dream, huh?
Having dinner with your idol—
I’m going back to my internship tomorrow.
Praew.
You’re just out of the hospital.
Don’t you think you should take a rest?
I know my strength better than anyone.
Come on, Phat.
Don’t force your sister.
Praew isn’t a kid anymore.
Am I right, you troublemaker?
Hello.
Yes.
I’ll submit it by the end of the day.
Excuse me.
I can pay for only one month right now…
Of course.
But if this becomes a three-month overdue,
your father has to move.
Of course.
I’m sorry.
(Breaking News: There’s been a fire
at Pratum Thani’s Palliative Care Center.)
(The fire was quickly out of control.)
(Forensic physicians are working overtime
to identify the deceased,)
(as many bodies are severely burned,
making it difficult for identification.)
Thank you.
Please let me do it, Editor.
I don’t mind what you pay me.
I’m okay with it.
Alright.
Hello.
(We like your work.)
(You can come in to collect your money.)
(I can give you 2000, excluding tax.)
Thank you.
I’ll make sure I get it done tonight.
Even if you changed your name
and your address,
you won’t get away.
Remember this.
Your dad may be dead,
but he still owes us money.
Dad, we have to run.
We’ll run so far they can’t find us.
Maybe…
The date of the first chapter publication?
It’s incorrect.
(Asura went to all this trouble
to lure youinto that abandoned building.)
His goal is for you to see
the ending he has planned.
(It has to be something you can guess.)
(And it must be something
only you and he know.)
Welcome back.
You have the perfect timing.
I have something fun planned.
You’ll love it.
I know you’re more mature now, Praew.
You’re mature enough to understand that,
sometimes, to unearth the truth,
pain is necessary.
When did I fall asleep?
I saw you sleeping
so I didn’t want to wake you.
We have one chance left.
Honestly,
I have no idea what the password could be.
What about Kitti?
This is my assumption.
Whoever is supporting Kitti
must be involved with the
Thai Investment Bank case 20 years ago.
It must be someone we have no idea about,
but Choti did.
So Kitti killed Choti to save this man?
He set up the murder scene
like Nekros did it,
and then framed me?
Yes.
The man Kitti serves
must be someone with enough power
to tamper with evidence.
If this falls apart,
it’s not even the case
I’m most worried about.
What are you worried about then?
You.
I’m worried you’d be targeted
before we find out the truth.
(The Nekros case reveals more questions
than answers as it stretches out,)
(especially when connected
to Inspector Yotsaphat Traikanawut,)
(the police officer initially
responsible for the case,)
(which reminds me of the saying)
(‘the apple doesn’t fall far
from the tree.’)
(I can’t help but question)
(if the death of one
of the detectives on this case,)
(Lieutenant Nopphan Kongkram,)
(whose death was quietly decided
to be a robbery,)
(could hide something bigger.)
(Maybe the only person who has an answer
is Inspector Yotsaphat himself.)
Who the hell gave him
this kind of information?
I did.
Praew.
He’s using you again.
He’s just connecting dots
that aren’t there for some rating.
I’m gonna ask you honestly.
Are you really okay he keeps publicly
shaming our dad’s name?
No one is using me.
And what he said about Dad is true.
Even if Thun didn’t say anything,
we couldn’t change what Dad did.
And you know why I agreed to this?
Because if your name
wasn’t in the spotlight,
you’d be killed like Nop was.
Actually… Praew has a point.
We have a lead on Kitti.
I have to go.
Take care of Praew for me.
Yeah.
I…
I understand you, Praew.
You did what you did
because you want to protect Phat.
But someone who thinks himself
a protector like him
would never understand.
Thun told me he gave you
all the chapters of Nekros.
Yes.
Thun was a Nekros fan.
That's why he downloaded all the chapters.
But Praew…
I actually don’t think
Thun is just a regular fan.
Are you suggesting Thun is Asura?
It’s possible.
I think this has gotten out of hand.
It’s obvious someone has him killed.
I’ll take care of the Kitti case myself,
but both you and I have to withdraw
from the Nekros case.
Because it’s now involved with
the Thai Investment Bank.
If we got involved,
it’d be against Article 157.
We’d be condemned for having something
to gain from the case.
What about Nop?
Phat.
Do you still have faith in me?
If you do, you must know a cop like me
will bring criminals to justice.
Or have you lost your faith?
Have you strayed into the way
of the devil like Nekros?
What is it?
Praew texted me the link
to Thun’s live broadcast.
(Hello, all.)
(I am not here to reveal some secrets
or give you an update on anything.)
(But I am here to communicate
with Mr. Kill directly.)
(I understand how you feel, Mr. Kill.)
(I understand how it feels
to watch the bad guys walk free.)
(I understand the pain that
made you create a monster like Nekros.)
(I don’t know if you’re watching,)
(but let me be the one to beg you
in place of all your fans…)
(Everyone is waiting for
the perfect ending of Nekros.)
(And if I were to guess, maybe the ending
is right where it all began.)
(Am I right, dai-sensei?)
Phat.
The term ‘dai-sensei.’
What? What about it?
‘Dai-sensei’ is the term
Asura calls Mr. Kill in the inbox.
It could be a coincidence.
I don’t think so.
To call Mr. Kill ‘dai-sensei’
on live broadcast,
he wants to send a message to Mr. Kill.
If Thun really is Asura,
revealing himself
on national television like this
means he’s up to something.
Right now, Praew is with him.
Praew could be in danger.
Sir, please wait.
What business do you have here?
Sir.
Wait up.
Oh, Mr. Kaye. Inspector.
Are you here to see me…
Oh, maybe you’re here to see Praew?
What’s the matter?
You called me dai-sensei.
Only one person in the world
calls me that.
What’s strange about that?
I’m a big fan of your work.
I don’t think there’s another word
befitting my respect for you as a fan.
I know what you’re thinking.
But I think there’s been
a misunderstanding about Thun.
And you, Phat.
As a cop, you should know…
this is no evidence.
I think we should go.
Sorry for intruding.
I’m pretty sure Thun has something to do
with the Thai Investment Back case.
There’s no other reason
why he won’t let this case go.
It’s possible.
Found it.
Thunwikorn Putthanan.
His parents were real estate agents
who got swindled
by the Thai Investment Bank.
They ended their own lives
to escape their debts.
Dad!
Which means…
Thun isn’t just a sensationalist reporter
jumping along on the Nekros hype.
If he really was the murderer,
this could be his motivation.
His life isn’t all that different from mine.
Well…
I’m going home.
Hey, Kaye.
Kaye.
Hello, Aunt Sri.
Kaye, it’s your father.
Come.
It’s your father.
Should we call an ambulance?
It’s okay, Dad.
It’s okay…
Uncle, why didn’t you tell me?
You were one of the investigators
on the Thai Investment Bank case.
COURT MARSHAL
INSPECTOR CHAIWAT TRAIKANAWUT
Yes.
It was true I was involved in
the Thai Investment Bank case.
But I wasn’t the main investigator.
Why didn’t you tell me?
Nekros is targeting you.
And those journalists are gonna
drag you into the spotlight.
I’ll have my men keep you safe.
No.
I won’t push back against this.
And I don’t need protection.
If I do, it means what those reporters
are digging up and trying to frame me for…
is true.
You do know
how every victim who said that
met their end?
Don’t worry about me.
My house has a top-notch security system.
You know if Nekros can’t do anything,
everything will have been a lie.
And I won’t even have
to make excuses for myself.
Am I right?
(…maybe the ending is right
where it all began.)
(Am I right, dai-sensei?)
(Right where it all began.)
CASE A045678
(Am I right, dai-sensei?)
PHAT
INCOMING CALL
Kaye.
Damn it.
Kaye!
Hey, Kaye!
Kaye.
It seems Mr. Kill has heard the plea
from me and his fans.
The ending of Nekros
was just uploaded minutes ago.
(And of course,
it brings us bigger questions.)
(Because the worst thing in the world
isn’t crimes committed by bad people,)
but the dishonesty from the people
who are supposed to be on justice’s side.
It is the perfect ending.
I don’t know who Nekros is pointing at.
But I can say for sure
that the worst thing is
when law enforcers themselves
are the bad guys.
Who would we turn to if that was the case?
Hey, Kaye.
Just listen to me.
You really think this will be over
just because you did this?
In the end, you’re just a tool…
(for Thun to use.)
I know this isn’t what you want.
Why are you quiet?
Talk to me!
(I’m sorry.)
Kaye.
Kaye! Kaye!
Shit!
Hello, Inspector.
Is anything out of the ordinary?
Everything is fine, sir.
Oh, your sister came over
to visit your uncle about an hour ago.
She left, though.
Thank you.
Uncle.
UNCLE CHAIWAT
(Oh, your sister came over
to visit your uncle about an hour ago.)
If it wasn’t for Nekros,
you’d have found Prim and me as corpses.
(His parents were real estate agents)
(who got swindled
by the Thai Investment Bank.)
(They ended their own lives…)
So Thun is another victim.
Someone who’s never been a victim like you
would never understand.
(There’s a type of murderer
called a mastermind.)
(He wouldn’t get his hands bloodied.)
(He borrows someone else’s hands
to do his dirty work.)
PRAEW
If I didn’t get Nop involved,
he wouldn’t have died.
Would he?
He wouldn’t have died…
Now that you know the whole truth,
how do you think all this crap
should end, Praew?
Take this story to the end.
If you don’t stop them now,
Praew will become a murderer
just like Kim did.
Will you promise me one thing?
Promise me you will protect the innocent.
Promise me you won’t let anyone
go through what I did.
I promise.